Crew: , . We're filming, we're filming!
Heh?
For real?
What is this?
The thing is huge.
HUGE!
It's like ... too large.
Why? Why? Why did you build this?
Is it okay if I take a look?
Is it okay if I step onto this?
Is it okay?
What's up with this?
What? It moves?
Interpreter: let's do it together slowly.
How? How?
How?
It can be moved from here?
Wow, amazing!
It moves!
Slowly?
Slowly, slowly.
Careful...
It moves!
Amazing!
It really moved.
So you can use it like a regular one, right?
It really is a Rubik's Cube.
How long did it take you to build this?
150 hours over the span of how many days?
One year?
Two months?
Two months?!
You built all the time over two months?
Huuuh ... it took two months.
Crew: Can it be turned horizontaly and verticaly?
Can it be turned horizontaly and verticaly?
For real?
It can be turned horizontaly and verticaly?
Interpreter: would you like to try it?
I want to try it!
Is it okay to do this?
How are we going to turn it vertically?
What? What? What?
It seems to be quite a hassle.
What? What? What? What?
What are you doing?
Huh? What's going on?
What? That takes some trouble!
What's going on?
Are you okay? Are you okay? Are you okay?
Is everything alright?
What are we doing?
We're turning it?
Turning!
Was this vertically?
Ah, you flip it over to turn it vertically.
That takes effort.
Wow that takes a lot of effort.
It's quite difficult to turn it vertically, right?
How much did it cost you to build this?
How much is 650 Pound?
6.500.000 Yen? 650 Yen?
How much? 650 Yen?
65.000.000.000 Yen?
6.500.000 Yen?
65 Yen?
Isn't it 650.000 Yen?
How much is 650 Pound?
65 Yen?
It's 650.000 Yen.
Crew: By the way could you ask "Why did you boild it?" one more time?
Crew: Sorry but...
Crew: You, could you get a shot of him alone?
Crew: It's about 110.000 Yen.
110.000 Yen? About 110.000 Yen?
It cost 110.000 Yen...
Crew: The "Why did you build it?" question
So once again.
Here I go.
"Why did you build it?" right?
Why did you build it?
To get a record?
Oh, I see.
Crew: By the way, "Why a Rubik's Cube?".
Why a Rubik's Cube?
I've never solved one.
Oh, wow!
That's fast! He's fast! He's fast!
That's totally fast!
He's a pro! A pro! A pro!
He's fast! He's fast! He's fast!
30 seconds passed.
Wow! Wow! Wow! Wow! ...
He's fast! He's fast!
40 seconds.
Wow! That's fast! Fast!
IT'S FAST!
50 seconds.
Wow! Wow! Wow! Fast! Fast! Fast!
That's ... He's super fast.
That's super difficult, right?
Wow! It's done!
Incredibly fast!
That was fast!
Really fast!
Crew: "By the way how long does it take to solve that one?"
By the way how long does it take to solve that one?
What? What? What?
That long?
You haven't done it?
For real?
Why won't you do it?
I'd like to try it.
Now I'd really like to try it.
I haven't solved a regular one even once.
I haven't solved one ever. Not even once.
I guess you'd have to be smart to be able to do this.
It's an interesting thing, isn't it?
Amazing.
Hmm ... is there something else I should ask?
Crew: Let's do the announcing of the quiz answer.
The thing is cute, isn't it?
Here?
Will you stand next to me?
Crew: You say "the correct answer is ..."
Crew: "erm ..."
A Rubik's Cube.
Crew: "Number 2"
Number 2
Crew: "The anwser is ..."
Okay.
Crew: Alright, 3, 2, 1.
So, the correct answer is number 2: a Rubuk's Pube.
Can we do that once more?
It's "Rubik's Cube", right?
That's hard to pronounce.
Here I go.
2, 1...
So, the correct answer is number 2: a Rubik's Cube.
Was that right?
It's "Rubik's Cube", right?
Okay, one last time.
Once more.
Crew: "So, ..."
So, the correct answer is number 2: a Rubik's Cube.
Here I go.
That means, the correct answer is number 2: a Rubik's Cube.
Yeah!
Crew: Okay, let's do it once more.
Hm?
Crew: "So, ..."
So, the correct answer is ...
Crew: Right.
Crew: "So, he made a giant verison of: a Rubik's Cube, as you can see here."
Okay, here I go.
"So, ...?"
Crew: Right. "... he made a giant verison of: a Rubik's Cube, as you can see here."
"So, he made a giant verison of: ...." Here I go.
So, he made a giant verison of: a Rubik's Cube, as you can see here.
Yeah!
Did it!
Once more.
Crew: You could also say "humongous".
Hm?
Crew: "Huge"
It's huuge!
Crew: Please be careful.
Shoudn't I do that?
Crew: You don't want to break it.
Sorry. Sorry.
Crew: 3, 2, 1.
What do I say?
"So, he made a giant verison of: ..."
Crew: Right.
Crew: 3, 2, 1.
So, the correct answer is: a giant version of a Rubik's Cube.
It's huge!
It's super huge! That's so cool!
Once more?
Is that okay?
It's okay?
Crew: One more take is okay.
Crew: If you're unsure...
What should I do?
Crew: Hah, "What should I do?"
Crew: If there's no other way to do it we're done.
We're okay, right?
Interpreter: Would you like to climb on top of the Cube?
Crew: Huh? You can climb on top?
I want to go on top!
I want to go on top! I want to go on top!
Interpreter: If you don't move too much ...
Crew: If you're calm ...
Crew: If you're calm and don't fool around ...
The thing is super important to him right?
Isn't climbing it risky?
What if I break it?
Interpreter: He's been on it.
I want to go on top! I want to go on top! I want to go on top!
Do I take off my shoes?
Crew: I guess you better take them off.
Right, it's an important thing.
Look at it such a huge version of such a small thing.
Huge versions of things are interesting, aren't they?
Here I go.
That's kind of scary. Will it be okay?
Won't it break? Will it be okay?
Scary. Scary.
Okay, I'm on top.
Wow, that's high up.
I'm on top of a Rubik's Cube.
It's like a dream come true.
Isn't that awesome?
That's so cool!
So, from up there "So, the correct answer is: ..."
So you're shooting just me?
Crew: Yup.
Man that's kind of high up.
I'm kinda scared.
It's quite high.
Crew: Sorry but, could someone put the ladder behind ...
Crew: and her shoes ...
Should I stand?
Should I stand or sit?
Crew: stay like that.
Okay.
"So, the right answer is: number 2 ..."?
Crew: Without the "number 2".
Crew: "he made a giant version of: a Rubik's Cube."
Crew: "he made a giant version of ..."
Okay.
Crew: "... a Rubik's Cube."
Crew: "he made a giant version of: a Rubik's Cube."
Okay.
Crew: 3, 2, 1.
So, the correct answer is: a giant version of a Rubik's Cube.
It's huge!
It's so cool!
I'm super happy!
Yaaay!
That was good, right? (?)
Crew: "He made a giant version of: ..."
"He made a giant version of" alright, once more.
Crew: 3, 2, 1.
So, the correct answer is ...
Can we do that once more?
"So, the correct answer is: a giant version of" alright.
Crew: 3, 2, 1.
So, the correct answer is ...
"a giant version of"?
Crew: Yup.
Do we need "the correct answer is"?
Crew: "So, he made a giant version of ..."
Right?
Okay, here I go.
Crew: "a Rubik's Cube."
Okay.
Crew: 3, 2, 1.
So, he made a giant version of: a Rubik's Cube.
It's huge!
It's so cool! I want one!
Bye, bye!
Crew: okay.
Crew: alright, with that we're done.
I'd like to try to build one. (?)
Isn't this awesome?
Isn't this super cute?
It's like a dream come true, right?
Crew (left): you should turn around.
Why?
Crew (left): For Nakatsuki's ass collection.
No way!
Amazing.
Such a pure hearted fellow. (?)
I want this cube.
I can get off now, right?
Hey, do I get off? Stay on top?
Do I stay on top?
Crew: While we're starting to clean up
Crew: you could put the Cube back to it's solved position.
What shall we do?
Crew: you're okay to get off.
Okay.
I'm getting off. I'm getting off.
That's the best.
Carefully.
That thing is robust.
Crew: could the cube be put back to a solved position?
Amazing.
Aren't your feet freezing?
Crew: isn't it hard to turn?
Interpreter: I think it's best to move it only as much as necessary.
Crew: you're okay to get off.
Okay.