Useless creations. YouTube: mudadukuri
Good evening. Fujiwara Marina here.
I create something useless every Friday,
so be sure to subscribe.
Today I'll create a candle in the shape of my face.
*Please be careful when using a stove.
And with that, it's done. The wax hardened.
Let's get it out of the mold.
I hope it will be easy to get out.
I got it out of the casting mold.
So, it's time to light it and get some Halloween atmosphere going.
Let's light it.
Romantic
Wasn't that super romantic?
A while ago I also created a chocolate version of my face.
If you're interested please check out the video.
Liked the video? Then subscribe and don't miss any upcoming videos.
See you next week.